https://ilovefundraising.com/privacy-notice/

Contact
0 item(s)
- $0.00
No products in the cart.
Contact
0 item(s)
- $0.00
No products in the cart.
Information about our organization and Web site
Your personal information is your business. Below is our privacy statement detailing how information collected by us is utilized.
We are based in the USA.
Our principal activity is: Fundraising
Our privacy policy covers Perkins Distributing Company and its Web sites:
Organization Name:
Perkins Distributing Company
Address:
PO Box 6882
City, Zip:
Tyler , 75711
State:
TX
Country:
USA
Controller:
Ronald Perkins
Web Sites(s):
www.perkinsdistributing.com
www.ilovecookiedough.info
Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access
You can access our Web sites home page and browse our sites without disclosing your personal data.
The services and links of our Web sites
Our Web sites may include functionality that allows users to review products and thereby communicate with other viewers of our website.
Perkins Distributing reserves the write to remove objectionable content and moderate the information as necessary.
Our Web sites do include links to third party Web service providers. Please be aware that Perkins Distributing Company is not responsible for the content on these other websites.
You may report a broken or objectionable link to mail@perkinsdistributing.com. You may also suggest helpful links as well.
Automatic Collection of Information
We do use cookies to facilitate our shopping cart functionality. No customer specific information is logged or recorded automatically. We do not link any information collected automatically with information from other websites or sources nor do we share information about web traffic of individuals unless required to do so by law.
Data Collection and Purpose Specification
Personal information is collected during the account creation and/or checkout purposes. The purpose of this collection is to facilitate order processing. Our secondary purpose of information collection is to make you aware of promotions and new product additions. We do not sell, rent, or share your information with any outside party. We may use information about purchases and preferences to identify trends and for marketing use inside Perkins Distributing
We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.
Access to the personal data we may hold about you
You may view the information we have collected from you by logging in to your account. If you are unable to login, please try the “forgot password” link or email: mail@perkinsdistributing.com
Privacy Support
Please call 903-581-0023 (M-F, 9 A.M. – 5 P.M. CST) with any questions about this statement or specific privacy concerns.
My Account | Conditions of Use | Privacy Notice | Secure Shopping | Shipping & Returns | Contact
© 2020 Perkins Distributing Company, PO Box 6882 Tyler, TX 75711-6882
‹
›
×
